qeon.co.id 2017-12-20

# Qeon Interactive | Giving The Best Gaming Experience for Indonesian Gamer

Qeon Interactive (hereinafter referred to as **QEON** ) and its affiliates (hereinafter referred to as **us** , **our** or **we** ) are dedicated to protect the privacy rights of our users (hereinafter referred to as **you** ). This Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as **Policy** ) describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information, including personal information that you provide or we collect in our websites (hereinafter referred to as **Sites** ) or any QEON game provided on a mobile platform (iOS and Android) collectively referred to as **Service**. The scope of this Policy is limited to information collected or received by QEON through your use of the Service. QEON is not responsible for the actions of third party people or companies, the content of their sites, the use of information you provide to them, nor any products or services they may offer.   
By using the Service, you are expressing your agreement to this Policy and the processing of your data, including your personal information in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Service. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
QEON collects information as described below. QEON’s primary goals in collecting and using information is to create your account, provide Services to you, improve our Service, contact you, conduct research and create reports for internal use. We store these information on our servers.  
In order to use your community forum, you must register and provide a username, password and email address. 

**QEON Sites**  
While you are browsing QEON's Sites, your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and referring website addresses may be logged automatically. We may use this information to monitor, develop and analyze your use of the Service. In addition, we may ask you to submit data that is personal to you, including but not limited to your name, profile photo, gender, age or birthday, links to your profiles on social networking websites, user names and e-mail and mail addresses. We may use this information to create a user profile and provide you services. 

**Social Media and Widgets**  
Our website uses Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**iOS and Android Platforms**  
When you use any of the QEON games or applications on a mobile platform, we may collect and record certain information such as your unique device ID, hardware type, media access control (“MAC”) address, international mobile equipment identity (“IMEI”), the version of your operating system (“OS”), your device name, your email address (if you have connected to Facebook or Google+), and your location (based on your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address). This information is useful to us for troubleshooting and helps us understand usage trends.  
We may collect your location-based information for the purpose of providing you with the correct version of the application. We will not share this information with third parties. If you no longer wish to allow us to track or use this information, you may turn it off on your device. Please note that the application may not work properly if we are unable to tell which country you are coming from.  
In addition, we create an unique ID to track your use of our Service. This unique ID is stored in your profile information to track the QEON games you are playing.  

**Facebook Connect, Game Center and Google+**  
You can log in to our site using sign-in services (“SN Service”) such as Facebook Connect and Apple’s Game Center. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address on our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.  
We may collect and record information through the SN Service in accordance with the policies and terms of that SN Service. The information we collect when you connect your user account to an SN Service may include: (1) your name, (2) your SN Service user identification number and/or user name, (3) address, city, province and country, (4) gender, (5) birth date, (6) email address, (7) profile picture or its URL, and (8) the SN Service user identification numbers for your friends that are also connected to QEON’s game(s).

**Invite a Friend**  
QEON may offer you the opportunity to invite your contacts from a SN Service (such as your Facebook friends) so that they can be located in QEON games and/or you can invite them to join you in QEON games. Such contact information will be used only for the purpose of sending communications to the addressee.

**Customer Service**  
We may collect your email address when you contact our customer service group and we may use that email address to contact you about your gaming experience with QEON games and notify you about our company news and promotions. 

**Push Notifications**  
We may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates, high scores and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you.

**Game Data Collection**  
Whenever you play our games, we collect data about all of your interactions with the game and with other players inside the game on server log files. This information may be associated with your player ID, IP address or device ID for the purpose of providing you our Services and improving them. 

**Other Collection**  
We may also acquire information from you through your access and participation in (1) message boards on the Service, (2) surveys regarding the Service or (3) sweepstakes or contest through the Service.  
We may provide you the opportunity to participate in a sweepstakes or contest through our Service. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these sweepstakes and contests are voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).  
We use this information to notify winners and award prizes. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these sweepstakes or contests; that company is prohibited from using your users’ personal information for any other purpose.

**Tracking Technologies**  
We use technologies such as cookies, scripts, and tags to identify a user’s computer/device and to “remember” things about your visit, such as your preferences or user name and password. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information, such as your user ID, for purposes such as improving the quality of our Services, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although you may not be able to access or use features of the Service.  
We may feature advertisements served by third parties that deliver cookies to your computer/device so the content you access and advertisements you see can be tracked. Since the third party advertising companies associate your computer/device with a number, they will be able to recognize your computer/device each time they send you an advertisement. These advertisers may use information about your visits to our Service and third party sites and applications in order to measure advertisement performance and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for the data collection practices of these third party advertisers, and we encourage you to check their privacy policies to learn more about their use of cookies and other technology.

**Mobile Analytics**  
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your device. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application.

**Third Party Services**  
Our services may contain third party tracking tools from our service providers, examples of which include Google Analytics which may use cookies, APIs, and SDKs in our services to collect and analyze user information on our behalf. The third parties may have access to information such as your device identifier, MAC address, IMEI, locale (specific location where a given language is spoken), geo-location information, and IP address for the purpose of providing their services under their respective privacy policies. Our privacy policy does not cover the use of tracking tools from third parties. We do not have access or control over these third parties.

**Ad Networks**  
We may feature advertising within our Service. The advertisers may collect and use information about you, such as your Service session activity, device identifier, MAC address, IMEI, geo-location information and IP address. They may use this information to provide advertisements of interest to you.   
In addition, you may see our games advertised in other services. After clicking on one of these advertisements and installing our game, you will become a user of our Service. In order to verify the installs, a device identifier may be shared with the advertiser.

**How We Use Information**  
We use information collected through our Service for purposes described in this Policy. For example, we may use your information to:  

  1. create game accounts and enable users to play our games;
  2. operate and improve our Service;
  3. understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our Service;
  4. respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  5. send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  6. communicate with you about promotions, rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by QEON and our selected partners;
  7. enable you to communicate with other users; and
  8. combine it with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your preferences and provide you with better services.

**Disclosure of Your information**  
QEON does not share your personal information except as described below:  

  1. With your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies.
  2. QEON may engage other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf. Example of these services include analyzing data and providing customer support. These agents and service providers may have access to your personal information in providing their service to QEON.
  3. We may release your information as permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law; investigate fraud, respond to a government request, enforce or apply our rights; or protect the rights, property, or safety of us or our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.
  4. We may share aggregate or anonymous information about you with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

**Changes to the Policy**  
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Security**  
QEON takes reasonable measures to protect your information from unauthorized access or against loss, misuse or alteration by third parties.  
While we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers" from illegally obtaining access to this information. We do not warrant or represent that your information will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties.

**Access to Personal Information**  
If Your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete inaccuracies by making the change within your account settings.

**Data Retention**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. 

**International Transfer**  
We may transfer information that we collect about you to affiliated entities, or to other third parties abroad. Please note that these countries and jurisdictions may not have the same data protection laws as Indonesia.
